<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>$ My Projects $ on TechXero Github</title>
    <link>https://techxero.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in $ My Projects $ on TechXero Github</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://techxero.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>^Xero-Linux^</title>
      <link>https://techxero.github.io/projects/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techxero.github.io/projects/linux/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s This ? This is where I will be posting information about my upcoming XeroLinux Arch-based Distro. It was made possible by Erik Dubois and the array of information over at the ArcoLinux site(s)&amp;hellip;
A lot of sleepless nights and hair-pulling later, I was able to build my own Distro, my way. Now hold your horses, I ill not be making it publicly available only to a few friends either locally or close by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calamares</title>
      <link>https://techxero.github.io/projects/calamares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techxero.github.io/projects/calamares/</guid>
      <description>About This is where I will be posting my custom Calamares Config. This can be used with various distros that use that installer, but mainly it was built with ArcoLinux in mind, specifically ArcoLinux Plasma. I do not know if it works with other D.E&amp;rsquo;s as I haven&amp;rsquo;t tested as of yet. I will soon, if you want you can test it and report back.
  How-To Ok, now for the &amp;ldquo;How-To Use&amp;rdquo; part of it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KVM Script</title>
      <link>https://techxero.github.io/projects/kvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techxero.github.io/projects/kvm/</guid>
      <description>About Kernel-Based Virtual Machine (KVM) is an open source virtualization technology built into Linux®. Specifically, KVM lets you turn Linux into a hypervisor that allows a host machine to run multiple, isolated virtual environments called guests or virtual machines (VMs). More-Info.
This is what I use for Virtualization, I find it does what I ned it to, and best part is, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t break like VirtualBox does when I use a custom Kernel like I do most of the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samba Script</title>
      <link>https://techxero.github.io/projects/samba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techxero.github.io/projects/samba/</guid>
      <description>About This is my easy-to-use Samba configurator &amp;amp; installer script, that I will keep up-to-date as much as I can. It was created using a combination of ArchWiki and Erik Bubois&#39; scripts merging all into one easy script that worked for me on every Arch-based Distro I used.
  How-To This script is dedicated to new-to-Linux users, click the link below, it will take you to script contents on my GitHub, copy code, create a new file wherever you want on your machine, calling it samba.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
